Guide to the Violet Hunt papers, 1858-1962.
Hunt, Violet papers, 1858-1962.
- Series I. Family
  - 1. Hunt family (Raine/Peacock/Hunt)
    - b. Manuscripts
      - Raine, James, 1791-1858. -- Apr. 28 -December 1858 (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
        With a typed statement about the proof of Alfred William Hunt's will. With handwritten sheet, possibly in James Raine's hand, containing extracts from the Deaton Register on the Peacock family. With original folder housing this material.
    - c. Documents
      - Peacock family -- [n.d.] (Box 3, Folder 18)
        AM(frag.) Genealogy
      - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- July 8, 1881-April 29, 1885 (Box 3, Folder 19)
        ADS Schedule of documents
        Held jointly with Margaret Raine Hunt.
      - Hunt, Andrew, d.1861 -- Aug. 9, 1861 (Box 3, Folder 20)
        AD Probate of the Will and Codice of Mr. Andrew Hunt decd.
        Written on vellum.
      - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- Mar. 27, 1874 (Box 3, Folder 21-a)
        ADS Under Seal of Confession--[contract]
        Contract with Sampson Low, Marston, Low, and Searle, signed by both parties.
      - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- Sept. 23, 1879 (Box 3, Folder 21-b)
        ADS Memorandum of Agreement
        Contract with Chatto & Windus, signed only "Chatto & Windus." Contract for an untitled work of fiction for publication in serial form in Belgravia.
  - 2. Ford family (Brown/Hueffer)
    - a. Correspondence
      - i. Catherine Brown Hueffer to and from Francis Hueffer
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [n.d.] (Box 4, Folder 1-a)
          ALS [init] to Catherine Brown Hueffer
          Dearest Cathy I have to go to the Italian opera/tonight
          2 ll. + envelope
          Catherine Brown Hueffer and Francis Hueffer were Ford Madox Ford's parents.
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Monday [n.d.] (Box 4, Folder 1-b)
          Dearest Cathy I received your letter late on Saturday
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Monday [n.d.] (Box 4, Folder 1-c)
          My dearest Cathchen, I have just arrived from Kelmscott
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Monday eve [n.d.] (Box 4, Folder 1-d)
          My darling Cathchen, I have been waiting all day/for a letter
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Tuesday [n.d.] (Box 4, Folder 1-e)
          My darling Puss, Many thousand thanks for your very/nice
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Tuesday [n.d.] (Box 4, Folder 1-f)
          My darling Puss I am very well although much/wanting to
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Tuesday [n.d.] (Box 4, Folder 1-g)
          My darling Cathchen Do come back to me today if you/can.
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Wednesday [n.d.] (Box 4, Folder 1-h)
          My sweet darling, I have three things to tell you which
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Wednesday evening [n.d.] (Box 4, Folder 1-i)
          Dearest Cathchen, I have this minute (9 p.m) received
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Thursday [n.d.] (Box 4, Folder 1-j)
          Dearest Cathy I am glad you are comfortably housed so far
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Thursday [n.d.] (Box 4, Folder 1-k)
          My darling Puss, As your last letter was a very short one
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Sunday night [n.d.] (Box 4, Folder 1-l)
          My darling Puss, You have written me a very nice letter
        - Hueffer, Catherine Brown -- [ca. 1870] (Box 4, Folder 2-a)
          ALS to Francis Hueffer
          Dearest Franz What a lovely morning it/is I am going
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Aug. 24, 1870 (Box 4, Folder 2-b)
          ALS to Catherine Brown Hueffer
          My dearest Cathy. I have just received your photographs
        - Hueffer, Catherine Brown -- [Sept. 28, 1870] (Box 4, Folder 2-c)
          I will not begin this letter in a correct/way
          4 ll. + envelope
        - Hueffer, Catherine Brown -- [Oct. 21, 1870] (Box 4, Folder 2-d)
          Dearest Franz I dare not ask Papa about any/thing this morning
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Tuesday [1871?] (Box 4, Folder 2-e)
          My dearest little Cathy, Appleton has [?] them today
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Friday [1871?] (Box 4, Folder 2-f)
          My dearest Cathy. Today I only write a few lines
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Saturday [1871?] (Box 4, Folder 2-g)
          My dearest Cathy, I send you some violets today
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Feb. 7 [1871?] (Box 4, Folder 2-h)
          My dearest Cathy, it is such a beautiful day today
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Apr. 11] 1871 (Box 4, Folder 2-i)
          My sweet little Kaethchen, I was just going to write to you
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Apr. 14, 1871] (Box 4, Folder 2-j)
          My dearest little Cathy, you are a very naughty girl
        - Hueffer, Catherine Brown -- [Apr. 21, 1871] (Box 4, Folder 2-k)
          Dearest Franz I spoke about your/fetching us
        - Hueffer, Catherine Brown -- [May 3] [1871?] (Box 4, Folder 2-l)
          Dearest Franz I shall answer your letter
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [May 25, 1871] (Box 4, Folder 2-m)
          My dearest little Cathy, What a difference there is
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Sept. 8, 1871] (Box 4, Folder 2-n)
          My dearest Cathy, I have just received a letter
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Nov. 17, 1871] (Box 4, Folder 2-o)
          My dearest little Caethchen, I feel much better this morning
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Nov. 20 [1871?] (Box 4, Folder 2-p)
          My dearest little Cathchen, I have just received your nice
        - Hueffer, Catherine Brown -- [Feb. 7] [1872?] (Box 4, Folder 3-a)
          My dearest Franz I am very stupid to have/told you
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Mar. 12, 1872 (Box 4, Folder 3-b)
          My dearest little Cathchen, I hope you have slept well
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Mar. 18, 1872] (Box 4, Folder 3-c)
          Mein lieber Liebchen Es ist moeglich dass ich morgen
          postcard
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Nov. 29, 1872] (Box 4, Folder 3-d)
          My dearest little Cathchen, The lecture has just come off
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Nov. 30, 1872 (Box 4, Folder 3-e)
          envelope
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Dec. 2, 1872] (Box 4, Folder 3-f)
          My dearest little Cathchen, I have just got your letter
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Mar. 26, 1873] (Box 4, Folder 3-g)
          My dearest Cathchen, I received your letter early this/morning
          2 ll. + 2 + envelope
          With letter from Marie Ophaven to Catherine Brown Hueffer, dated March 22, 1873 and mentioned in Francis Hueffer's letter.
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Sept. 5, 1873] (Box 4, Folder 3-h)
          My dearest little Cathchen, We have just arrived
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Mar. 26, 1874 (Box 4, Folder 3-i)
          My sweet Cathchen, What a short letter you have written to/me
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Apr. 29, 1874 (Box 4, Folder 3-j)
          Two envelopes
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [May 15, 1874] (Box 4, Folder 3-k)
          My dearest darling. Coming home I found a letter/from
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [June 10, 1874] (Box 4, Folder 3-l)
          My darling Cathchen, Just a line to tell you that the/pre
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Oct. 2, 1874] (Box 4, Folder 3-m)
          Dearest Pussie, I will come on Saturday to dinner as/you
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Mar. 14, 1875] (Box 4, Folder 4-a)
          My darling Puss, You must not be angry with me
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Mar. 25, 1875] (Box 4, Folder 4-b)
          My darling Puss I must write you a short letter tonight
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Mar. 27, 1875] (Box 4, Folder 4-c)
          My dear Puss, I was a little cross with you/yesterday
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Apr. 8, 1875] (Box 4, Folder 4-d)
          My darling Puss, I have just received you little note
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Apr. 9, 1875] (Box 4, Folder 4-e)
          My darling Puss, I do want you to go very much
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Apr. 20, 1875 (Box 4, Folder 4-f)
          My dearest Puss This came last night; it is very
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Apr. 22, 1875] (Box 4, Folder 4-g)
          My darling Puss, Why have you not written to me?/I hope
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Apr. 27, 1875] (Box 4, Folder 4-h)
          My darling Puss, Why have you not written to me/as you
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Apr. 29, 1875 (Box 4, Folder 4-i)
          My darling Puss, This is just the day for
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [May 19, 1875] (Box 4, Folder 4-j)
          My darling Puss Why have you not written/to me as you
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- May 21, 1875 (Box 4, Folder 4-k)
          My darling Puss, I will certainly come to the Sqre/on Monday
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [June 15, 1875] (Box 4, Folder 4-l)
          My darling Puss, I have received the enclosed letter
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- June 19, 1875 (Box 4, Folder 4-m)
          Darling Puss, I send the key to my portmanteau
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Aug. 23, 1875] (Box 4, Folder 4-n)
          My darling Puss, Enclosed the cheque for £8 that/is £1
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Oct. 14, 1875] (Box 4, Folder 4-o)
          My darling Puss, I send you a letter that has arrived/for you.
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Oct. 18, 1875] (Box 4, Folder 4-p)
          Darling little Pussie, I am back in Merton and the house/is
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Feb. 16, 1876] (Box 4, Folder 5-a)
          My darling Puss, I have got your letter this morning short but
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Feb. 17, 1876] (Box 4, Folder 5-b)
          Darling Puss, You are a very naughty girl not to have written
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Mar. 5, 1876] (Box 4, Folder 5-c)
          My darling Puss, That was a very nice sweet letter
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Mar. 9, 1876] (Box 4, Folder 5-d)
          My darling Puss, I am glad you are going to the play and
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Apr. 20, 1876] (Box 4, Folder 5-e)
          My darling Puss, Only a line to tell you that Fordie and
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Apr. 21, 1876] (Box 4, Folder 5-f)
          Darling Puss, This is the order. I got letters today
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [June 3, 1876] (Box 4, Folder 5-g)
          My darling Puss, I am afraid you are angry with me
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Aug. 9, 1876 (Box 4, Folder 5-h)
          My darling little Puss, Here I am still at [?] with plenty/of
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [Aug. 14, 1876] (Box 4, Folder 5-i)
          My darling little Puss, Here I am at Bayreuth and last night
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- [July 16, 1879] (Box 4, Folder 5-j)
          My darling Puss, I have not answered your sweet little letter
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Nov. 25, 1882 (Box 4, Folder 6-a)
          My darling Puss I was very glad to have your letter and yo
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Dec. 20, 1882 (Box 4, Folder 6-b)
          My darling Puss, I am afraid our Xmas now will be very
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Oct. 17, 1886 (Box 4, Folder 6-c)
          My darling Puss, I arrived late last night at this hotel
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Oct. 17, 1886 (Box 4, Folder 6-d)
          ALS to Mrs. Hueffer [Francis Hueffer's mother]
          Dear old Mamma, I came back sound and safe from Leeds/last
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Oct. 20, 1886 (Box 4, Folder 6-e)
          Dear old Mamma, I write again to say that we are/all snug
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Nov. [25?], 1886 (Box 4, Folder 6-f)
          My darling Puss Just a line to tell you that the lecture
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Dec. 29, 1886 (Box 4, Folder 6-g)
          Dearest Cathy, In spite of a fearful snowstorm I got/home
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Jan. 28, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 6-h)
          Darling Cathy I arrived here safely last night after a/very
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Feb. 5, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 6-i)
          My darling Puss, Your letter has just arrived and was quite
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Aug. 27, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 6-j)
          Dear old Mamma The enclosed paragraph appears in The Times
          (with the clipping mentioned in Francis Hueffer's letter)
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Sept. 1, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 6-k)
          My darling Puss, I have not written to you before because/I
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Oct. 12, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 6-l)
          Dear old Mamma, Just a line to say that I arrived safely and
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Oct. 22, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 6-m)
          Dear old Mamma, I got yours and Poppy's letter and am/very
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Oct. 27, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 6-n)
          Dear old Mamma, I have not written to you before partly/because
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Nov. 14, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 6-o)
          Dearest Cath, I was very glad to see from your letter that you
          1 l. + envelope
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Nov. 19, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 6-p)
          Dearest Cathy, Morill MacKenzie being away at San Remo
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- May 7, 1888 (Box 4, Folder 6-q)
          Dear old Mama, I am very glad to see from your/letter that you
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- May 9, 1888 (Box 4, Folder 6-r)
          Dearest Cathy, You said in your first letter most distinctly
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- May 12, 1888 (Box 4, Folder 6-s)
          Dear old Mama, I have just arrived and found every-/thing
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889. -- Sept. 1, 1888 (Box 4, Folder 6-t)
          Dear old Mamma, I came back this morning and Ford has/just
      - ii. General correspondence to the Ford family
        - Anthony, Mark, 1817-1886. -- [n.d.] (Box 5, Folder 1)
          ALS to Ford Madox Brown
          18 Monmouth Road, Bay ? Dear Brown I am very/much obliged to you
          With envelope with names written in pen in Violet Hunt's hand and typed note by V.H.
        - Boyd, Alice -- May 2, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 2)
          Penkill Castle, Ayrshire My dear Cathy I live so out of/the world now
        - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893. -- Thursday night [n.d.] (Box 5, Folder 3-a)
          ALS to Emma Madox Brown (Mrs. Ford)
          1, St. Edmunds Terrace My Dearest, I have been at the Town Hall
        - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893. -- July 13, 1878 (Box 5, Folder 3-b)
          37 Fitzroy Square W. Dear Love, I send you herein the/half
        - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893. -- [n.d.] (Box 5, Folder 3-c)
          ALS to Editor of Dictionary of National Biography
          Manchester Dear Sir, Noticing your request in the Athe-/naum
        - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893. -- Nov. 29, 1880 (Box 5, Folder 3-d)
          Manchester Dear Frank, My wife has just read your/note
        - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893. -- May 1, 1859 (Box 5, Folder 3-e)
          [n.p.] My dear Hunt The evening at Patmores/when you
        - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893. -- Sept. 7, 1862 (Box 5, Folder 3-f)
          14 Grove Terrace, Kentish Town N.W. My dear Hunt, I find myself under the/necessity of writing
          With annotation by Alfred Hunt.
        - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893. -- Dec. 4, 1870 (Box 5, Folder 3-g)
          37 Fitzroy Square W. My dear Alfred Hunt, If I have delayed so long/in answering you
        - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893. -- June 14, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 3-h)
          AL[draft]S to Theodore Watts
          1 St. Edmund Terrace, Regents Park N.W. My Dear Watts I enclose you the Acct in question
        - Brown, Oliver Madox, 1855-1874. -- Sept. 25 [1872?] (Box 5, Folder 4-a)
          37 Fitzroy Square My dear Hueffer When I received
        - Brown, Oliver Madox, 1855-1874. -- [July 27, 1874] (Box 5, Folder 4-b)
          37 Fitzroy Square Dear Mrs Hunt, It gives me great grief
          With envelope
        - Burne-Jones, Edward Coley, Sir, 1833-1898. -- [Nov. 2, 1872] (Box 5, Folder 5)
          [London] dear Huffer That I dont ?/over to-day
        - Casey, D. -- [1847] (Box 5, Folder 6)
          ALS [frag.] to Ford Madox Brown
          [n.p.] ...impardonnable oui je serais
        - Cole, Henry, Sir, 1808-1882. -- Nov. 5, 1880 (Box 5, Folder 7)
          [West Brompton, S.W.] Dear Sir I send you the/3d. Report
        - Davison, James William, 1813-1885. -- Thursday [1877?] (Box 5, Folder 8-a)
          [n.p.] How can you see/mountains in molehills?
          Signed "T. Q." (Theophilus Queer).
        - Davison, James William, 1813-1885. -- Friday morning [1877?] (Box 5, Folder 8-b)
          [n.p.] Hueffer! Read Frederic/Soulie's Comte de/Toulouse
          Signed "Theophilus Queer".
        - Davison, James William, 1813-1885. -- Jan. 29 [1877?] (Box 5, Folder 8-c)
          ALS(init.) to Francis Hueffer
          36 Tavistock Place Dr. Hueffer - Dont forget to go
        - Davison, James William, 1813-1885. -- Feb. 22, 1877 (Box 5, Folder 8-d)
          36 Tavistock Place My dear Hueffer Oxenford died this/morning
        - Davison, James William, 1813-1885. -- [Feb. 28, 1877] (Box 5, Folder 8-e)
          [n.p.] My dear Hueffer - I am too sincere a friend
        - Davison, James William, 1813-1885. -- [Mar. 1, 1877] (Box 5, Folder 8-f)
          [n.p.] My dear Anaximander Thales anxaimenes
        - Davison, James William, 1813-1885. -- [Apr. 8, 1877] (Box 5, Folder 8-g)
          36 Tavistock Place Dr Hueffer - You must come to-/morrow
        - Davison, James William, 1813-1885. -- Nov. 20 [1877] (Box 5, Folder 8-h)
          36 Tavistock Place Dear Merlin (Ambrosius) Dont come here/on Wednesday
        - Garnett, Richard, 1835-1906. -- Oct. 18, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 9-a)
          British Museum Dear Mrs. Hueffer Thank-you for your letter.
        - Garnett, Richard, 1835-1906 -- Jan. 14, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 9-b)
          British Museum Dear Mrs Hueffer, I have both your letters
        - Garnett, Richard, 1835-1906 -- Jan. 22, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 9-c)
          British Museum Dear Mrs Hueffer, I have just received/a cheque
        - Garnett, Richard, 1835-1906 -- Jan. 28, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 9-d)
          British Museum Dear Mrs Hueffer, Thank-you for your/letter.
        - Garnett, Richard, 1835-1906 (continued) -- Jan. 28, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 9-d)
        - Garnett, Richard, 1835-1906. -- July 20, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 9-e)
          London Dear Mrs Hueffer, Thanks for your last/letter.
        - Grove, George, Sir, 1820-1900. -- Dec. 12, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 10)
          Kensington Gore, London, S.W. Dear F.H. I am ashamed to/bother you
        - Houghton, Richard Monckton Milnes, Baron, 1809-1885. -- Jan. 26 [1874] (Box 5, Folder 11)
          ALS to Franz Hueffer
          Ferrybridge Dear Vi I thank you much/for your book.
        - Hueffer, Bertha -- Feb. 11, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 12)
          Paris Dear Mrs Hueffer. I received yesterday a postal card
          With "The English Review" envelope which held the letters from Ford Madox Ford's German relatives to his father, mother, and brother Oliver.
        - [Hueffer], Emma -- May 11, 1870 (Box 5, Folder 13)
          Muenster Lieber Franz. [?] gibt mir
          Emma Hueffer was Francis Hueffer's sister and Ford Madox Ford's aunt.
        - Hueffer, F. -- June 14, [19]10 (Box 5, Folder 14)
          ALS to [?]
          26 Cumming Str. Pentonwille N. Sehr geehrter Herr! Ihrem Liebens wuerdigen Wunsche
        - Hueffer, Francis, 1845-1889. -- Dec. 24, 1856 (Box 5, Folder 15)
          ALS to his father, ? Hueffer
          [n.p.] Hoc festocarissima mater gratulor
        - Hueffer, Hermann -- Feb. 29, 1870 (Box 5, Folder 16-a)
          Bonn Lieber Franz. Seinen [?] brief mit
          Hermann Hueffer was Francis Hueffer's half-brother and Ford Madox Ford's uncle.
        - Hueffer, Hermann -- May 3/4, 1870 (Box 5, Folder 16-b)
          Bonn Lieber Franz! Dir
        - [Hueffer?], Sophia -- May 4, 1870 (Box 5, Folder 17)
          Muenster Lieber Franz. 2 ll. + 1
          Sophia [Hueffer?] was a German relation of Ford Madox Ford's.
        - Hueffer, Wilhelm -- July 22, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 18-a)
          San Passerario Dear Cathy I received from Rome your/letter
          Wilhelm Hueffer was Francis Hueffer's half-brother and Ford Madox Ford's uncle.
        - Hueffer, Wilhelm -- Dec. 22, 1870 (Box 5, Folder 18-b)
          Florence Lieber Franz
        - Hueffer, Wilhelm -- Sept. 5, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 18-c)
          ALS to Oliver Hueffer
          San Passerario Dear Oliver I received your letter
          Oliver Hueffer was Ford Madox Ford's brother.
        - Ireland, John, 1879-1962. -- Mar. 13, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 19)
          Chelsea, S.W. Dear Mrs. Hueffer An [earliest set]/work of mine is going to/be played
        - MacKenzie, Alexander Campbell, Sir, 1847-1935. -- Aug. 24, 1885 (Box 5, Folder 20)
          Lower [?] Dear Hueffer It is understood that/your share of the foreign
        - Miller, Thomas, b. 1839. -- May 31, 1857 (Box 5, Folder 21-a)
          Liverpool My Dear Mr Brown I hope you have/now got over
        - Miller, Thomas, b. 1839. -- June 28, 1857 (Box 5, Folder 21-b)
          Liverpool My Dear Sir I received your very/kind & welcome
        - Miller, Thomas, b. 1839. -- Apr. 18, 1858 (Box 5, Folder 21-c)
          Liverpool My Dear Mr Brown I have your long &/kind letter
        - Miller, Thomas, b. 1839. -- Apr. 3, 1861 (Box 5, Folder 21-d)
          Liverpool My Dear Mr Brown I have your/kind letter of 1st
        - Miller, Thomas, b. 1839. -- Apr. 4, 1861 (Box 5, Folder 21-e)
          Liverpool My Dear Mr Brown I had that pleasure/yesterday
        - Miller, Thomas, b. 1839. -- [Aug.?] 2, 1862 (Box 5, Folder 21-f)
          Liverpool My Dear Mr Brown I have to thank you/for your long kind letter
        - Montgomery, Edmund -- Nov. 4, 1899 (Box 5, Folder 22-a)
          Hempstead, Texas Dear Mrs Hueffer I am very grateful to/you
        - Morris, William, 1834-1896. -- [1871] (Box 5, Folder 22-b)
          Empty envelope addressed to Francis Hueffer
        - Mozley, Miss -- Sept. 6, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 23)
          [Leamington?] Miss Mozley encloses/Mrs Hueffer another
        - National Gallery (London) -- May 9, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 24-a)
          National Gallery, London Dear Madam I am requested by the/Director
          Written and signed by Charles L. Eastlake.
        - National Gallery (London) -- July 16, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 24-b)
          National Gallery, London Dear Madam I write to acknowledge/the receipt
        - National Portrait Gallery Offices -- Apr. 26, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 25-a)
          Westminster, S.W. Dear Madam I am extremely sorry that
          Written and signed by George Scharf.
        - National Portrait Gallery Offices -- May 11, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 25-b)
          Westminster, S.W. Dear Madam I have this afternoon received
        - National Portrait Gallery Offices -- June 27, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 25-c)
          Westminster, S.W. Dear Madam In accordance with the/ instruction
        - National Portrait Gallery Offices -- June 20, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 25-d)
          Westminster Madam. The Trustees of the National Portrait
          Gallery